You are looking at a living,
breathing, interactive ecosystem that I built for my AI agents
so that I could gamify my entire life
and all my businesses and everything.
And within this little ecosystem,
we built these two factory rooms that run autonomous businesses.
And the first autonomous business we started was an Etsy store.
On this conveyor belt here is a representation of that Etsy store.
We could actually access the Etsy store and see how much we've made
and manage the store from this little dashboard here.
And yes, we have about 40 orders on the Etsy store so far.
We're just about to hit $2,000 in revenue.
And the biggest question I've been asked has been about the Etsy store
actually. And I want to go over how you guys at home
can build your own autonomous Etsy store that runs
entirely on its own with your AI agents.
So what you're gonna need first is AI agents.
You're gonna need about three.
I recommend at least having about three AI agents.
So let me start from step 1,
research agent. This is Nova.
Nova hangs out in his little research lab
and all he does is throughout the day,
he'll do research on Etsy,
on products that are performing well on Etsy,
on stores that are performing well on Etsy
and how we can take inspiration from those stores
and apply it to our own Etsy store. Right?
So he'll take that research and he'll Bring it over to forge over here
and forge has access to Printify and Nano Banana Pro.
So you're gonna need Nano Banana Pro which is Google,
which is Gemini which will cost you about $20 a month.
This gives your agent access to actually design products.
So that is step one step two is actually gonna be an Etsy store.
This will cost you about $30 to start a seller account on Etsy
and you're gonna need a Printify account.
Printify has all of these products right here
and you can have your agent slap your
or the designs it creates on these templates here
in which Printify will actually
when you get an order on your Etsy store
will print your design on
that your AI agent made and ship it out to your customer for you right?
And all you have to do is connect your Printify API key to your agent,
connect your Etsy API key to your agent
to your main factory agent
and then that is essentially all it needs to start creating products
So Etsy Printify and then Gemini Nano Banana Pro to create the designs
right? And then you're probably asking what is the third agent?
Do you have research agent?
You have the agent that makes the designs and puts it on Etsy
over here we have the media agent
which pumps out TikToks all day
and actually helps me with my YouTube channel and stuff like that
but forge Will create the product photos from these templates
and he'll take these template photos.
Not exactly these. Usually they're like the empty,
like there's no model on them.
Usually he takes like we take these usually so that it looks clean,
right?
And he'll take these product photos he creates and give them to Pixel
and Pixel will actually curate slideshows and post it on TikTok.
So that is essentially all you need to have an entirely
autonomous Etsy store. The only thing I would recommend other than that
is to create this system here,
which I created when I first started the Etsy store.
I don't really use this anymore,
but forge, when he started designing in his early career,
he was trash. His designs looked terrible.
So what I did is I built this system,
this approval reject system,
a feedback system. So he would show me a design.
I would either say approve,
I like it or reject. This shit is garbage.
And I did this a few hundred times with him.
It took about two or three days.
And now
he's at the point where I completely trust him to make products.
His products are great. So that's what I would recommend doing
is definitely setting up some sort of system at first
so that you can train your agent to actually produce what you want.
And yeah, that's how you start up your own Etsy store.